investitwisely.com 2014-06-17

# Privacy Policy | Invest It Wisely

Your privacy is important to Invest It Wisely. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that Invest It Wisely collects, and the ways in which Invest It Wisely uses that personal information. We never sell your personal information to third parties. This privacy policy may be updated; please check this page occasionally to keep up to date with any changes.

#### Log Files

We collect and use the data contained in log files, which are generated automatically by the server. The information contained therein includes your IP address, ISP, browser, pages visited, as well as the time visited.

#### **Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). Third party advertisers on the site may also use cookies and web beacons, and may include Google Analytics in addition to Google Adsense. In order to disable this behavior, you can deactivate our cookies or third party cookies via your browser settings.

#### Third-party policies

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

Data controlled by third parties is under the control of their respective privacy policies. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party. Please see the policies below for more information:

<http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>  
<http://www.google.com/privacy.html>

#### Contact

Please contact us if you have any concerns, questions, or comments.
